[
  {
    "user_id": "1310740562",
    "username": "Nanashi_Kuro",
    "role": "Клиент",
    "question": "Роль",
    "answer": "Клиент",
    "timestamp": "2025-04-11T07:15:35.594335"
  },
  {
    "user_id": "1310740562",
    "username": "Nanashi_Kuro",
    "role": "Клиент",
    "question": "Идея приложения",
    "answer": "Класс",
    "timestamp": "2025-04-11T07:15:52.583044"
  },
  {
    "user_id": "1310740562",
    "username": "Nanashi_Kuro",
    "role": "Клиент",
    "question": "Готовность использовать",
    "answer": "Готов платить",
    "timestamp": "2025-04-11T07:15:55.640298"
  },
  {
    "user_id": "1310740562",
    "username": "Nanashi_Kuro",
    "role": "Клиент",
    "question": "Готовность использовать",
    "answer": "Готов платить",
    "timestamp": "2025-04-11T07:15:58.242926"
  },
  {
    "user_id": "1310740562",
    "username": "Nanashi_Kuro",
    "role": "Клиент",
    "question": "Готовность использовать",
    "answer": "Готов платить",
    "timestamp": "2025-04-11T07:15:58.929713"
  },
  {
    "user_id": "1310740562",
    "username": "Nanashi_Kuro",
    "role": "Клиент",
    "question": "Готовность использовать",
    "answer": "Нет",
    "timestamp": "2025-04-11T07:16:00.381830"
  },
  {
    "user_id": "1310740562",
    "username": "Nanashi_Kuro",
    "role": "Клиент",
    "question": "Готовность использовать",
    "answer": "Готов платить",
    "timestamp": "2025-04-11T07:16:02.103452"
  },
  {
    "user_id": "1310740562",
    "username": "Nanashi_Kuro",
    "role": "Клиент",
    "question": "Готовность использовать",
    "answer": "Если бесплатно",
    "timestamp": "2025-04-11T07:16:02.596401"
  },
  {
    "user_id": "1310740562",
    "username": "Nanashi_Kuro",
    "role": "Открытый ответ",
    "question": "Комментарий",
    "answer": "Да норм",
    "timestamp": "2025-04-11T07:16:28.734759"
  },
  {
    "user_id": "1310740562",
    "username": "Nanashi_Kuro",
    "role": "Клиент",
    "question": "Роль",
    "answer": "Клиент",
    "timestamp": "2025-04-11T07:16:51.769168"
  },
  {
    "user_id": "1310740562",
    "username": "Nanashi_Kuro",
    "role": "Клиент",
    "question": "Идея приложения",
    "answer": "Не очень",
    "timestamp": "2025-04-11T07:16:55.919670"
  },
  {
    "user_id": "1310740562",
    "username": "Nanashi_Kuro",
    "role": "Клиент",
    "question": "Готовность использовать",
    "answer": "Готов платить",
    "timestamp": "2025-04-11T07:16:59.559326"
  },
  {
    "user_id": "1310740562",
    "username": "Nanashi_Kuro",
    "role": "Клиент",
    "question": "Готовность использовать",
    "answer": "Если бесплатно",
    "timestamp": "2025-04-11T07:17:01.177754"
  },
  {
    "user_id": "1310740562",
    "username": "Nanashi_Kuro",
    "role": "Клиент",
    "question": "Готовность использовать",
    "answer": "Если бесплатно",
    "timestamp": "2025-04-11T07:17:02.311880"
  },
  {
    "user_id": "1310740562",
    "username": "Nanashi_Kuro",
    "role": "Клиент",
    "question": "Готовность использовать",
    "answer": "Если бесплатно",
    "timestamp": "2025-04-11T07:17:02.611371"
  },
  {
    "user_id": "1310740562",
    "username": "Nanashi_Kuro",
    "role": "Клиент",
    "question": "Готовность использовать",
    "answer": "Если бесплатно",
    "timestamp": "2025-04-11T07:17:04.261677"
  },
  {
    "user_id": "1310740562",
    "username": "Nanashi_Kuro",
    "role": "Клиент",
    "question": "Готовность использовать",
    "answer": "Если бесплатно",
    "timestamp": "2025-04-11T07:17:07.517035"
  },
  {
    "user_id": "1310740562",
    "username": "Nanashi_Kuro",
    "role": "Клиент",
    "question": "Готовность использовать",
    "answer": "Нет",
    "timestamp": "2025-04-11T07:17:23.112009"
  },
  {
    "user_id": "1310740562",
    "username": "Nanashi_Kuro",
    "role": "Открытый ответ",
    "question": "Комментарий",
    "answer": ".",
    "timestamp": "2025-04-11T07:17:25.861041"
  },
  {
    "user_id": "1310740562",
    "username": "Nanashi_Kuro",
    "role": "Клиент",
    "question": "Роль",
    "answer": "Клиент",
    "timestamp": "2025-04-11T07:17:30.497097"
  },
  {
    "user_id": "1310740562",
    "username": "Nanashi_Kuro",
    "role": "Клиент",
    "question": "Идея приложения",
    "answer": "Не понял идею",
    "timestamp": "2025-04-11T07:17:35.491016"
  },
  {
    "user_id": "1310740562",
    "username": "Nanashi_Kuro",
    "role": "Мастер",
    "question": "Роль",
    "answer": "Мастер",
    "timestamp": "2025-04-11T07:18:10.229188"
  },
  {
    "user_id": "1310740562",
    "username": "Nanashi_Kuro",
    "role": "Мастер",
    "question": "Идея приложения",
    "answer": "Неинтересно",
    "timestamp": "2025-04-11T07:18:16.650270"
  },
  {
    "user_id": "1310740562",
    "username": "Nanashi_Kuro",
    "role": "Мастер",
    "question": "Причина отказа",
    "answer": "Не полезно",
    "timestamp": "2025-04-11T07:18:36.125218"
  },
  {
    "user_id": "1310740562",
    "username": "Nanashi_Kuro",
    "role": "Открытый ответ",
    "question": "Комментарий",
    "answer": "укпукп",
    "timestamp": "2025-04-11T07:18:39.359170"
  },
  {
    "user_id": "1310740562",
    "username": "Nanashi_Kuro",
    "role": "Мастер",
    "question": "Роль",
    "answer": "Мастер",
    "timestamp": "2025-04-11T07:18:44.417168"
  },
  {
    "user_id": "1310740562",
    "username": "Nanashi_Kuro",
    "role": "Мастер",
    "question": "Идея приложения",
    "answer": "Не очень",
    "timestamp": "2025-04-11T07:18:48.687038"
  },
  {
    "user_id": "1310740562",
    "username": "Nanashi_Kuro",
    "role": "Мастер",
    "question": "Идея приложения",
    "answer": "Не очень",
    "timestamp": "2025-04-11T07:18:49.670515"
  },
  {
    "user_id": "1310740562",
    "username": "Nanashi_Kuro",
    "role": "Мастер",
    "question": "Идея приложения",
    "answer": "Не очень",
    "timestamp": "2025-04-11T07:18:49.825912"
  },
  {
    "user_id": "1310740562",
    "username": "Nanashi_Kuro",
    "role": "Мастер",
    "question": "Идея приложения",
    "answer": "Класс",
    "timestamp": "2025-04-11T07:19:06.760042"
  },
  {
    "user_id": "1310740562",
    "username": "Nanashi_Kuro",
    "role": "Мастер",
    "question": "Платная версия",
    "answer": "Нет",
    "timestamp": "2025-04-11T07:19:09.274920"
  },
  {
    "user_id": "1310740562",
    "username": "Nanashi_Kuro",
    "role": "Мастер",
    "question": "Платная версия",
    "answer": "Да",
    "timestamp": "2025-04-11T07:19:11.135941"
  },
  {
    "user_id": "1310740562",
    "username": "Nanashi_Kuro",
    "role": "Открытый ответ",
    "question": "Комментарий",
    "answer": "ыыы",
    "timestamp": "2025-04-11T07:19:13.956244"
  },
  {
    "user_id": "1310740562",
    "username": "Nanashi_Kuro",
    "role": "Мастер",
    "question": "Роль",
    "answer": "Мастер",
    "timestamp": "2025-04-11T07:19:19.609127"
  },
  {
    "user_id": "1310740562",
    "username": "Nanashi_Kuro",
    "role": "Мастер",
    "question": "Идея приложения",
    "answer": "Класс",
    "timestamp": "2025-04-11T07:19:22.891927"
  },
  {
    "user_id": "1310740562",
    "username": "Nanashi_Kuro",
    "role": "Мастер",
    "question": "Платная версия",
    "answer": "Да",
    "timestamp": "2025-04-11T07:19:27.347719"
  },
  {
    "user_id": "1310740562",
    "username": "Nanashi_Kuro",
    "role": "Мастер",
    "question": "Платная версия",
    "answer": "Да",
    "timestamp": "2025-04-11T07:19:28.086671"
  },
  {
    "user_id": "1310740562",
    "username": "Nanashi_Kuro",
    "role": "Клиент",
    "question": "Роль",
    "answer": "Клиент",
    "timestamp": "2025-04-11T07:21:13.569665"
  },
  {
    "user_id": "1310740562",
    "username": "Nanashi_Kuro",
    "role": "Клиент",
    "question": "Идея приложения",
    "answer": "Не очень",
    "timestamp": "2025-04-11T07:21:16.597352"
  },
  {
    "user_id": "1310740562",
    "username": "Nanashi_Kuro",
    "role": "Клиент",
    "question": "Готовность использовать",
    "answer": "Нет",
    "timestamp": "2025-04-11T07:21:21.212420"
  },
  {
    "user_id": "1310740562",
    "username": "Nanashi_Kuro",
    "role": "Открытый ответ",
    "question": "Комментарий",
    "answer": "Ybxtuj",
    "timestamp": "2025-04-11T07:21:28.303843"
  },
  {
    "user_id": "1310740562",
    "username": "Nanashi_Kuro",
    "role": "Клиент",
    "question": "Роль",
    "answer": "Клиент",
    "timestamp": "2025-04-11T07:21:39.853391"
  },
  {
    "user_id": "1310740562",
    "username": "Nanashi_Kuro",
    "role": "Клиент",
    "question": "Роль",
    "answer": "Клиент",
    "timestamp": "2025-04-11T07:22:40.713274"
  },
  {
    "user_id": "1310740562",
    "username": "Nanashi_Kuro",
    "role": "Клиент",
    "question": "Идея приложения",
    "answer": "Класс",
    "timestamp": "2025-04-11T07:22:46.326829"
  },
  {
    "user_id": "1310740562",
    "username": "Nanashi_Kuro",
    "role": "Клиент",
    "question": "Готовность использовать",
    "answer": "Готов платить",
    "timestamp": "2025-04-11T07:22:48.118224"
  },
  {
    "user_id": "1310740562",
    "username": "Nanashi_Kuro",
    "role": "Открытый ответ",
    "question": "Комментарий",
    "answer": "200",
    "timestamp": "2025-04-11T07:22:50.999504"
  },
  {
    "user_id": "1310740562",
    "username": "Nanashi_Kuro",
    "role": "Клиент",
    "question": "Роль",
    "answer": "Клиент",
    "timestamp": "2025-04-11T07:23:22.247471"
  },
  {
    "user_id": "1310740562",
    "username": "Nanashi_Kuro",
    "role": "Клиент",
    "question": "Идея приложения",
    "answer": "Класс",
    "timestamp": "2025-04-11T07:23:25.036665"
  },
  {
    "user_id": "1310740562",
    "username": "Nanashi_Kuro",
    "role": "Клиент",
    "question": "Готовность использовать",
    "answer": "Если бесплатно",
    "timestamp": "2025-04-11T07:23:25.909699"
  },
  {
    "user_id": "1310740562",
    "username": "Nanashi_Kuro",
    "role": "Мастер",
    "question": "Роль",
    "answer": "Мастер",
    "timestamp": "2025-04-11T07:23:35.992930"
  },
  {
    "user_id": "1310740562",
    "username": "Nanashi_Kuro",
    "role": "Мастер",
    "question": "Идея приложения",
    "answer": "Неинтересно",
    "timestamp": "2025-04-11T07:23:38.099383"
  },
  {
    "user_id": "1310740562",
    "username": "Nanashi_Kuro",
    "role": "Мастер",
    "question": "Причина отказа",
    "answer": "Не полезно",
    "timestamp": "2025-04-11T07:23:44.198294"
  },
  {
    "user_id": "1310740562",
    "username": "Nanashi_Kuro",
    "role": "Мастер",
    "question": "Роль",
    "answer": "Мастер",
    "timestamp": "2025-04-11T07:23:54.324022"
  },
  {
    "user_id": "1310740562",
    "username": "Nanashi_Kuro",
    "role": "Мастер",
    "question": "Идея приложения",
    "answer": "Не очень",
    "timestamp": "2025-04-11T07:23:56.285160"
  }
]